Guide to the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Collection of Dissertations and Theses RG.26.35
New York University Archives
- Series II: Education, Health, and Nursing Theses, 1950-1989; 6 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons
  - A Study to Formulate Principles of Nursing Pertaining to Nursing Diagnosis and Nursing Therapy Which Underlie Professional Nursing Practice by Dorothy McMullan, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The Relationship Between Sociability and Personal Space Preferences Among College Students in the Morning and in the Afternoon by Janet A. Rodgers, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The Relations Among Measures of State Anxiety, Critical Thinking Ability and Judged Duration of Individuals During and After a Disruptive Life Event by Diane W. Scott, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 12)